Guide to the Western Wood Products Association Records 1909-1970
Oregon Historical Society, Research Library
- West Coast Lumbermen's Association Records, 1909-1970; Subgroup 1; 60 linear ft. (40 document cases; 28 record cartons; 3 boxes Oversize A—11x14; 6 boxes Oversize B-1—16x20)
  - Branches and Associated Organizations, 1911-1965; Series C
    - Records from Various Organizations, 1911-1963; Subseries 3
      - National Lumber Manufacturers Association (NLMA) and Industry Representatives—trade association histories, 1959; 1963 (Box-folder 38/7)
      - National Lumber Manufacturers Association (NLMA) Special Committee on Grade Simplification and Standardization—minutes, 1960 (Box-folder 38/8)
      - Pacific Lumber Inspection Bureau and F.O.B. Mill—standard schedules of pricing, dimensions, and grading rules, 1912; 1917; 1922; 1925-1926; 1929; 1951 (Box-folder 38/9)
      - West Coast Dry Kiln Club—minutes, 1941-1947 (Box-folder 39/1)
      - West Coast Lumber Trade Extension Bureau—annual reports, 1926-1927 (Box-folder 39/2)
      - West Coast Lumber Trade Extension Bureau—membership directories, 1928 (Box-folder 39/3)
      - West Coast Lumber Trade Extension Bureau—minutes, 1926-1929 (Box-folder 39/4)
      - West Coast Woods—promotional literature and reports, 1946-1950; 1953 (Box-folder 39/5-6, Box 76)
      - Western Homes Foundation—press releases and printing mats for home designs, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 39/7, Box-folder 40/1-2)
      - Western Timber Structures—minutes, 1937 (Box-folder 40/3)
      - Willamette Valley Lumbermen's Association— Barometer, 1940-1948 (Box 68)
        The periodicals contained in Box 68 have been bound into volumes.
      - The Lumber Estimator and The Official Box Estimator and The Lumber Estimator, 1911 (Box-folder 40/4)
      - Lumber Calculator, Southern Yellow Pine Grading Rules and Perpetual Piece Price List, 1926; 1929; 1937 (Box-folder 40/5)
      - Pocket Manual on Forest Laws and Practice for the Douglas Fir Region and The Lumberman's Actuary, 1944-1947 (Box-folder 40/6)